Stereographic Cards
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Stereographic Cards, 2.1.8
  - Keystone View Company Stereographic Library, "Tour of the World", volumes IX and X, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 1 (Box 1608)
    - [no description], 73
    - Verso, 73-verso
    - [no description], 74
    - Verso, 74-verso
    - [no description], 75
    - Verso, 75-verso
    - [no description], 76
    - Verso, 76-verso
    - [no description], 77
    - Verso, 77-verso
    - [no description], 78
    - Verso, 78-verso
    - [no description], 79
    - Verso, 79-verso
    - [no description], 80
    - Verso, 80-verso
    - [no description], 81
    - Verso, 81-verso
    - [no description], 82
    - Verso, 82-verso
    - [no description], 83
    - Verso, 83-verso
    - [no description], 84
    - Verso, 84-verso
    - [no description], 85
    - Verso, 85-verso
    - [no description], 86
    - Verso, 86-verso
    - [no description], 87
    - Verso, 87-verso
    - [no description], 88
    - Verso, 88-verso
    - [no description], 89
    - Verso, 89-verso
    - [no description], 90
    - Verso, 90-verso
    - [no description], 91
    - Verso, 91-verso
    - [no description], 92
    - Verso, 92-verso
    - [no description], 93
    - Verso, 93-verso
    - [no description], 94
    - Verso, 94-verso
    - [no description], 95
    - Verso, 95-verso
    - [no description], 96
    - Verso, 96-verso
    - [no description], 97
    - Verso, 97-verso
    - [no description], 98
    - Verso, 98-verso
    - [no description], 99
    - Verso, 99-verso
    - [no description], 100
    - Verso, 100-verso
  Box 1609
- Stereographic Cards, 2.1.8
  - Keystone View Company Stereographic Library, "Tour of the World", volumes XI and XII, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 1 (Box 1609)
    - [no description], 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
    - [no description], 2
    - Verso, 2-verso
    - [no description], 3
    - Verso, 3-verso
    - [no description], 4
    - Verso, 4-verso
    - [no description], 5
    - Verso, 5-verso
    - [no description], 6
    - Verso, 6-verso
    - [no description], 7
    - Verso, 7-verso
    - [no description], 8
    - Verso, 8-verso
    - [no description], 9
    - Verso, 9-verso
    - [no description], 10
    - Verso, 10-verso
    - [no description], 11
    - Verso, 11-verso
    - [no description], 12
    - Verso, 12-verso
    - [no description], 13
    - Verso, 13-verso
    - [no description], 14
    - Verso, 14-verso
    - [no description], 15
    - Verso, 15-verso
    - [no description], 16
    - Verso, 16-verso
    - [no description], 17
    - Verso, 17-verso
    - [no description], 18
    - Verso, 18-verso
    - [no description], 19
    - Verso, 19-verso
    - [no description], 20
    - Verso, 20-verso
    - [no description], 21
    - Verso, 21-verso
    - [no description], 22
    - Verso, 22-verso
    - [no description], 23
    - Verso, 23-verso
    - [no description], 24
    - Verso, 24-verso
    - [no description], 25
    - Verso, 25-verso
    - [no description], 26
    - Verso, 26-verso
    - [no description], 27
    - Verso, 27-verso
    - [no description], 28
    - Verso, 28-verso
    - [no description], 29
    - Verso, 29-verso
    - [no description], 30
    - Verso, 30-verso
    - [no description], 31
    - Verso, 31-verso
    - [no description], 32
    - Verso, 32-verso
    - [no description], 33
    - Verso, 33-verso
    - [no description], 34
    - Verso, 34-verso
    - [no description], 35
    - Verso, 35-verso
    - [no description], 36
    - Verso, 36-verso
    - [no description], 37
    - Verso, 37-verso
    - [no description], 38
    - Verso, 38-verso
    - [no description], 39
    - Verso, 39-verso
    - [no description], 40
    - Verso, 40-verso
    - [no description], 41
    - Verso, 41-verso
    - [no description], 42
    - Verso, 42-verso
    - [no description], 43
    - Verso, 43-verso
    - [no description], 44
    - Verso, 44-verso
    - [no description], 45
    - Verso, 45-verso
    - [no description], 46
    - Verso, 46-verso
    - [no description], 47
    - Verso, 47-verso
    - [no description], 48
    - Verso, 48-verso
    - [no description], 49
    - Verso, 49-verso
    - [no description], 50
    - Verso, 50-verso
    - [no description], 51
    - Verso, 51-verso
    - [no description], 52
    - Verso, 52-verso
    - [no description], 53
    - Verso, 53-verso
    - [no description], 54
    - Verso, 54-verso
    - [no description], 55
    - Verso, 55-verso
    - [no description], 56
    - Verso, 56-verso
    - [no description], 57
    - Verso, 57-verso
    - [no description], 58
    - Verso, 58-verso
    - [no description], 59
    - Verso, 59-verso
    - [no description], 60
    - Verso, 60-verso
    - [no description], 61
    - Verso, 61-verso
    - [no description], 62
    - Verso, 62-verso
    - [no description], 63
    - Verso, 63-verso
    - [no description], 64
    - Verso, 64-verso
    - [no description], 65
    - Verso, 65-verso
    - [no description], 66
    - Verso, 66-verso
    - [no description], 67
    - Verso, 67-verso
    - [no description], 68
    - Verso, 68-verso
    - [no description], 69
    - Verso, 69-verso
    - [no description], 70
    - Verso, 70-verso
    - [no description], 71
    - Verso, 71-verso
    - [no description], 72
    - Verso, 72-verso
    - [no description], 73
    - Verso, 73-verso
    - [no description], 74
    - Verso, 74-verso
    - [no description], 75
    - Verso, 75-verso
    - [no description], 76
    - Verso, 76-verso
    - [no description], 77
    - Verso, 77-verso
    - [no description], 78
    - Verso, 78-verso
    - [no description], 79
    - Verso, 79-verso
    - [no description], 80
    - Verso, 80-verso
    - [no description], 81
    - Verso, 81-verso
    - [no description], 82
    - Verso, 82-verso
    - [no description], 83
    - Verso, 83-verso
    - [no description], 84
    - Verso, 84-verso
    - [no description], 85
    - Verso, 85-verso
    - [no description], 86
    - Verso, 86-verso
    - [no description], 87
    - Verso, 87-verso
    - [no description], 88
    - Verso, 88-verso
    - [no description], 89
    - Verso, 89-verso
    - [no description], 90
    - Verso, 90-verso
    - [no description], 91
    - Verso, 91-verso
    - [no description], 92
    - Verso, 92-verso
    - [no description], 93
    - Verso, 93-verso
    - [no description], 94
    - Verso, 94-verso
    - [no description], 95
    - Verso, 95-verso
    - [no description], 96
    - Verso, 96-verso
    - [no description], 97
    - Verso, 97-verso
    - [no description], 98
    - Verso, 98-verso
    - [no description], 99
    - Verso, 99-verso
    - [no description], 100
    - Verso, 100-verso
  Box 1610
- new, 2.1.8
  - Keystone View Company Stereographic Library, "World War", volume I, circa 1930s; 1 (Box 1610)
    - [no description], 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
    - [no description], 2
    - Verso, 2-verso
    - [no description], 3
    - Verso, 3-verso
    - [no description], 4
    - Verso, 4-verso
    - [no description], 5
    - Verso, 5-verso
    - [no description], 6
    - [no description], 7
    - Verso, 7-verso
    - [no description], 8
    - Verso, 8-verso
    - [no description], 9
    - Verso, 9-verso
    - [no description], 10
    - Verso, 10-verso
    - [no description], 11
    - Verso, 11-verso
    - [no description], 12
    - Verso, 12-verso
    - [no description], 13
    - Verso, 13-verso
    - [no description], 14
    - Verso, 14-verso
    - [no description], 15
    - Verso, 15-verso
    - [no description], 16
    - [no description], 17
    - Verso, 17-verso
    - [no description], 18
    - [no description], 19
    - [no description], 20
    - [no description], 21
    - [no description], 22
    - [no description], 23
    - [no description], 24
    - Verso, 24-verso
    - [no description], 25
    - Verso, 25-verso
    - [no description], 26
    - Verso, 26-verso
    - [no description], 27
    - Verso, 27-verso
    - [no description], 28
    - Verso, 28-verso
    - [no description], 29
    - Verso, 29-verso
    - [no description], 30
    - Verso, 30-verso
    - [no description], 31
    - Verso, 31-verso
    - [no description], 32
    - Verso, 32-verso
    - [no description], 33
    - Verso, 33-verso
    - [no description], 34
    - Verso, 34-verso
    - [no description], 35
    - Verso, 35-verso
    - [no description], 36
    - Verso, 36-verso
    - [no description], 37
    - Verso, 37-verso